luckstars.co 2017-10-05

# Security & Privacy Policy | Best Casinos Free spins Slots, Games and Bonuses online

If you view and use this website you are agreeing with the following Security & Privacy Policy, together with our disclaimer and terms of use.

The term LuckStars or ‘us’ or ‘we’ refers to the owner of the website.  
The term ‘you’ or ‘your’ refers to the user or viewer of our website.

  1. **      Privacy**  
We take your security and privacy seriously. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website. You can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. LuckStars is committed to respect your privacy and to comply with applicable data protection and privacy laws and we have therefore provided this Privacy Policy to help you understand how we collect and use your details and offering you gaming offers. If you do not understand the Privacy Policy then you are invited to send in your questions to [promos@luckstars.com](mailto:promos@luckstars.com) and we will do our best to answer your questions in full as quickly as possible. This Privacy Policy is subject to change. Please check it regularly. We reserve the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and in response to changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation. We may use your information to improve our website and services. We will frequently send you promotional, newsletter emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided when registering.
  2. **      Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
  3. **      Cookies**  
Cookies provide information regarding the computer used by a user. We may use cookies to gather information about your computer in order to assist us in improving our website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. We may gather information about your general internet use by using the cookie. Where used, those cookies are downloaded to your computer and stored on the computer’s hard drive. Such information will not identify you personally. It is statistical data. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever. You can adjust the settings on your computer to decline any cookies if you wish. This can easily be done by activating the reject cookies setting on your computer.
  4. **      Analytic Demographics**  
We use analytic demographics systems such as Google Analytic on this website and Re-marketing to advertise online. Therefore, third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet.
  5. **      Links to other websites**  
Our site contain links to third party websites. Once you have used those links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control on their website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting those sites and those sites are not governed by this privacy statement. We do not control the content or links or offers that appear on those sites and are not responsible of them. Those sites, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. Those sites have their own privacy policies and terms of use policies, you should look at those statements applicable to the website in question.
  6. **      Controlling your personal information**  
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting.
  7. **      Opting-Out**  
Once you register you agree that we may send you emails regarding the Site, promotions and newsletter. You may choose not to receive future emails from us by selecting an unsubscribe link at the bottom of emails that you receive from us.

This Security & Privacy Policy is subject to change. We reserve the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and in response to changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation.

Last updated on 23/02/2016.

1 person likes this
